easycanvasprints.com 2013-11-22

# Privacy Policy | EasyCanvasPrints

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ is committed to protecting your privacy while providing quality services that give you an enjoyable and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ website and governs data collection and usage. By using the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. The EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ website is the website contained at http://www.EasyCanvasPrints.com and all pages and subpages therein.

## Collection of your Personal Information

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ collects personally identifiable information when you register or order, such as your e-mail address, physical address, name, and phone number, and credit card information. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ also collects information not personally identifiable, such as zip code, city and state.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by EASY CANVAS PRINTS™. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses, templates made, path through the site, and operating system information. This information is used by EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ for the operation of its services, to maintain quality of service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ web site.

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ web site.

## Use of your Personal Information:

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ collects and uses your personal information to operate the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ web site and deliver the services you have requested. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ also uses your personally identifiable information from time to time to inform you of other products or services available from EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ and its affiliates. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Note that at any time you may opt out of being contacted by EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ for any research or product updates, through clear links at the bottom of every email.

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to EASY CANVAS PRINTS™, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ keeps track of the web sites and pages our customers visit within and from the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ web site, in order to determine what EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of EASY CANVAS PRINTS™; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of EASY CANVAS PRINTS™, or the public.

## Use of Cookies

The EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ web site may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you register with the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ site or services, a cookie helps EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ services or Web sites you visit.

## Security of your Personal Information

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ will not record, store, or save your Credit Card Number without your express consent and notice from EASY CANVAS PRINTS™.

## Changes to this Statement

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that EASY CANVAS PRINTS™ has not adhered to this Statement, please use the inquiry form to contact us. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
